List below - in the planned order you will implement them (first at the top) - your ideas for how you will make your mechanical turk behave.  Give brief reasons why you think each feature is important, and why you have chosen to implement them in this order.

1.  Mr Pass - starts spinoff if has resources, otherwise passes.  Why first? This is required to be the first Turk everyone submits.
    - can never win as it only has 2 campuses on far vertices (that is, it only gets 2 types of students)

1.5. Mr Pass 2.0 - trades available resources for MJ, MTV and MMONEY (the required resources to create spinoffs).
    - prioritises MJs over MTVs and MMONEYs as MTVs and MMONEYs can be lost when a 7 is rolled.

2.  Mr Build ARCs + Pass - Does the same thing as Mr Pass, as well as trying to make as many ARCs as possible to earn the prestige award for most ARCs, passes when doesn't have resources for ARCs or spinoffs.
    - looks for vacant arcs that are adjacent to arcs or unis that it already owns.
    - builds arcs on these and tries to create the longest continuous ARC.
    - has a very slim chance of winning, provided the starting campuses are at BQN and BPS. Each ARC is worth 2KPI, so if it can Patent IP (worth 10KPI) + initial KPI (20), as well as have the prestige award for most ARCs (10KPI) & most publications (10KPI), it would also need to build 50 ARCs to win the game.

3.  Mr Build Campus + ARCs + Pass - Does the same thing as before, as well as building campuses.
    - has 3 cases for Uni A, B & C
    - campuses require: BPS, BQN, MJ, MTV
    - scans for closest regions with BPS, BQN, MJ or MTV. Builds ARC towards these regions and builds a campus on it.

3.5  Mr Build Campus 1.5 - scans board for reguions with dice values and prioritises numbers closer to 7. If these regions are BPS, BQN, MJ or MTV it will try to build there, unless it already owns 2 of these types of campuses

4.  Mr Campus 2.0 - First seeks to acquire the closest retraining centres and then seeks to build campuses in the corresponding colours to the retraining centres. 

5.  Mr Build GO8 + Campus + ARCs + Pass - Does the same thing as before, but also looks to build GO8s whenever possible.



Write below the plan you and your Turk Pair partner have devised to ensure you will be an effective team:

- Communicate via iMessage
- Utilise GitHub
- Use time efficiently
- Delegate tasks